# **NAKUL DESHMUKH**

Vinkar Colony, Manewada, Nagpur, Maharashtra – 440027 email-nakuldeshmukh619@gmail.com

Mobile No. 9028838663 Linkedin - @nakuldex

#### **SUMMARY**

Veteran and L3 certified Python Developer with 5+ years of relevant experience. Automated 300+ variety of manual processes. Working independently and leading a small team. Strong in analytical, technical and automation opportunity hunting skills. Delivered plenty of End-to-end and easy to maintain automated process solutions. Currently serving as Tech lead.

### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

**Organization: Wipro Technologies** 

Client: Intel

30/03/2017 to Present day Pune (Remote), India 01/04/2021 to Present Day

- An Open-source project where Pytest based framework was developed for Automated testing with team of 7-8 people. Integrated with CICD pipeline for nightly executions.
- Contributing to Open-source Linux OS project by Automating tests. (Linux Testing program).
- Learned new Automation Techniques, Frameworks, and security.
- Gained expertise in Selenium, PyTest, Pandas, Linux CLI, API building.
- Hands on experience on deploying and managing applications on AWS.
- Experience of CICD pipeline building maintaining.
- Hard earned expertise in clear Logic building, problem solving and critical thinking.
- Delivered Automation as a Service project (AaaS) i.e., an end-to-end Test automation framework with 400+
   Test cases hosted on CICD platform. AaaS includes webpage automation using Page-object model, improved
   XPATHs definitions and Selenium, CLI automations using Paramiko, & API triggers/Microservices using Flask.
- Worked with teams across locations for Power BI automation. Independently created Python Glue scripts
  that reconcile data from different sources into one for Power BI tool. Quickly learned Pandas, RE and
  MySQL for this work.

Client: Chemours

30/03/2017 to 31/03/2021 Pune/WFH. India

- SAP based project with diversified technologies, our team was in improving process and automating the potential flows. Had got chance to work upon industry leasing automation tools and techs.
- Learned business communication skill, interacted with clients across the world, made good professional relations
- Started working on Automation challenges with this project. Developed scripts for Automated infra
  monitoring, DB access management, SAP ticket/ID creation, User access management. Enabled teams to
  achieve SLA targets by building live Dashboard and Saved 1300+ manual hours. Participated in 'Botathon
  2021' for Automation Anywhere skills.
- Learned to troubleshoot and maintain legacy automation scripts. Analysis of Reports.
- Contributed to NPT v10 development by working on backend using Java 8 skill.
- Helped HR team by building easy to use Resume parser based on ML model.

#### **SKILLS**

Python, Java 8, DSA	Automation Anywhere,	Git, Jira,	CICD, Microservices,
Selenium, XPaths, Sikuli,	Linux, Windows, AWS	Pytest, Pandas, Flask	SQL, Logic building

## **EDUCATION**

M. Tech (Work integrated) in IT with 8.2 CGPA.

### **B. Sc** in Statistics with 7.0 CGPA

## **INTRESTS AND HOBBIES**

- Like to play guitar and keyboard.
- Tutor for Statistics, Coding.
- Following technical trends and ROBO science topics.